Xing.
النجوم
Keep an eye on the store.
انظر إلى المتجر
I'll deliver some goods.
سأذهب لإرسال البضائع
I'll be back soon.
سأعود بعد قليل
Wei Xing.
وي شينغ
Check out my Huashan Swordsmanship!
انظر إلى مهارتي في سيف هوا شان
Xixing Magic sucks her IQ away.
سحر امتصاص النجوم سحب ذكائها
Demon, go away!
أيها الشيطان ابتعد
A bunch of fools.
مجموعة من الأحمق
Shall we go in and look for it?
ما رأيك أن ندخل ونبحث
It's getting dark.
سيظلم السماء قريباً
What if something dangerous
ماذا لو كان في الداخل
happened to himin there?
ماذا لو واجه أي خطر
Ke.
شياو كو
Let's go.
هيا
Be careful.
انتبهي
Flashlight! Ting!
المصباح  تينغ تينغ
Okay.
حسناً
Slow down.
ببطء ببطء
Diqiu.
الأرض
Wang.
لاو وانغ
No way.
مستحيل
Can he really be here?
هل يمكن أن يكون هنا حقا
Diqiu, are you there?
هل الأرض موجودة؟
Diqiu?
الأرض
What's wrong with Wang?
ماذا حدث لاو وانغ
He got us ending up here.
‫جعلتنا في هذا المكان‬
It's okay.
لا بأس لا بأس
Don't be afraid. It's just a rock.
لا تخافي، إنه مجرد قطع الحجر
Diqiu, are you there?
هل الأرض موجودة
Diqiu.
الأرض
Wang.
لاو وانغ
Did you
أنتم
hear that sound?
هل تسمعون ذلك الصوت؟
What sound?
ما هذا الصوت
The story my mother told me
عندما كنت صغيرة
She said
قالت
there's a girl living here
هناك شخص يعيش فيه
who always dances
‫بمجرد سماع الموسيقى‬
when she hears music.
‫دائماً ترقص‬
The one  chosen by her
‫الشخص الذي تم اختياره‬
will never come out.
‫لن يخرج أبدا‬
Do you like my dancing shoes?
هل تحبين حذائي؟
Don't scream. I'm more scared.
‫لا تصرخ لا تصرخ أخاف من الصراخ‬
Don't scare yourselves.
لا تخيفوا أنفسكم
The four of us can beat one.
لا يمكننا هزيمته نحن الأربعة
Yes.
نعم
Let's go.
لنذهب
Those ghosts
تلك الشياطين
are just illusions set up in fear.
هم خيال يصنع الناس لنفسهم في الخوف
Don't be afraid.
لا تخافوا
But there's really sound.
لكن هناك صوت حقا
This is my music box when I was young.
‫هذا صندوق موسيقي في طفولتي‬
So you're the little girl who can dance.
‫اتضح أن الفتاة التي تستطيع الرقص هي أنت‬
Look what I found.
‫انظر ماذا وجدت
Dear Guo Ting, congratulations
‫عزيزي قوه تينغ تهانينا لكونك عضوة لنا
on joining us as a real princess.
أصبحت أميرة صغيرة حقيقية
Look.
انظر إلى هذا
Ultramen are having a meeting here.
‫أوترامان يقيم اجتماع كبير هنا
When did Robinson become Luffy?
‫متى أصبح لو بين سون لو في
Am I supposed to be King of the Pirates?!
‫هل تريدني أن أكون ملك اللصوص
No need to say more.
لا داعي أن أقول
You know who did it, right?
هل تعرفون من فعل ذلك؟
Wang, what's wrong with you?
‫لاو وانغ ما بك‬
You made us here. It's so scary.
‫جعلتنا هنا مخيف جدا‬
Let’s go.
هيا
Wang Diqiu.
‫وانغ الأرض‬
What's going on?
ماذا حدث
You scared us to death.
لقد أخفتنا حتى الموت
So beautiful.
جميل جدا
So this is what's outside the cave.
اتضح أن خارج الكهف هكذا
Wang.
لاو وانغ
Ting, slow down.
تينج تينج تمهلي
You might fall.
احذري من السقوط
It looks like you're about to jump.
يبدو أنك ستقفز في البحر عندما تقف هناك
Be careful.
انتبهي
Why are you acting so depressive here alone?
لا تتظاهر بوحدك
Isn't it pretty?
أليس جميلاً؟
It's really beautiful from here.
‏إنها جميلة حقاً‏
I only start to feel like a senior now.
‫حتى الآن أشعر بالصف الثالث‬
But isn't it
لكن
too late?
قد فات الأوان
Do you know how many time zones there are?
هل تعرف كم منطقة في العالم؟
24.
24 -نعم -
There is an hour difference
في كل منطقة
between every time zone.
هناك فرق ساعة
But it doesn't mean
لكن هذا لا يعني
the time we have is more or less
ما نملكه
than the people in the other time zones.
أكثر من شخص في منطقة أخرى
So relax.
لذا استرخي
We are not behind or leading.
‫لم نتراجع ولا نتقدم‬
We are just on time
فقط في منطقتنا الخاصة
in our own time zone.
في الوقت المحدد
If I jump down like this,
إذا قفزت هكذا
will I reach the other side?
السباحة إلى المقابل
Do it and we'll know.
للتدريب على الحقيقة
Ting, you can try it.
تينج تينج يمكنك المحاولة
And throw you into the sea.
ارميك في البحر
We're coming, senior year!
‏نحن في الصف الثالث‏
Please be kind to us.
يرجى معاملتنا بشكل جيد
I hope all our wishes can come true.
آمل أن تتحقق أمنيتنا
If you want to abuse someone, choose others.
إذا كنت تريد معاملة الآخرين
Please bless us, senior year.
باركنا في الصف الثالث
College entrance examination, we are here!
لقد جئنا في امتحان القبول الجامعي
That's when I realized
أدركت هذا اليوم
that many things in life
أن الكثير من الأشياء في الحياة
are like this black cave.
مثل كهف هي شان
For example, our senior year life.
مثلا حياتنا في الثانوية
Before we experienced it,
قبل أن نجرب
we always heard various stories
دائما ما سمعنا
from our parents.
من والديك
But only after experiencing it,
لكن بعد التجربة بنفسي
we would see the surprises in truth.
‫عرفت الحقيقة دائماً ما يحدث شيء غير متوقع‬
But fortunately,
لكن لحسن الحظ
you never have to face it alone.
لا يجب أن تواجهي وحدك أبدا
Someone will always
سيكون هناك شخص
protect you.
لحمايتك
September 15, USA's fourth investing bank,
‫اليوم الخامس عشر من سبتمبر البنك الاستثماري الرابع في أمريكا
Rehman Brothers, announced bankruptcy.
‫أعلن شركة ريمان للإفلاس
It's been two months.
منذ شهرين
This incident also signifies
‫هذه القضية علامة أيضا
a global financial tsunami.
ظهور سوناري المالي العالمي
Experts say this phenomenal financial crisis
حسب تحليل الخبير فإن أزمة المالية هذه المرة فارغة
will impact some of the domestic companies.
سيؤثر على بعض الشركات الوطنية
Why hasn't it been quiet for a year?
لماذا لم يتوقف هذا العام
I went out for a walk.
خرجت للتجول للتو
I heard the neighbors say
سمعت الجيران يقولون
the rice was bought out.
تم سرقة الأرز
Mom, don't listen to them.
أمي لا تستمعي إلى الشائعات
At the critical moment,
كلما كان الأمر أكثر أهمية
we should trust our government.
علينا أن نثق في حكومنا
I don't think
أنا أيضًا أعتقد
we can't buy food in such a big country.
لا يمكننا شراء الحبوب في بلدنا الكبير
That's right. How is that possible?
نعم كيف يمكن ذلك
Are you buying or not?
هل ستشتري أم لا
No.
لا
Dad, mom.
أبي أمي
I report Guo Ting.
أبلغ قوه تينغ
She bought a lipstick with breakfast money.
اشترت أحمر الشفاه مقابل الفطور
Enough.
حسنا
Stop.
توقف توقف
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعلون
Did you fall down?
سقطت
Stop messing around in morning.
استيقظ في الصباح الباكر
Time to go to school.
تنتظر الدراسة
I won't stop your mom if she hits you again.
إذا ضربتك أمك مرة أخرى لن أمسك بها
Yes.
نعم
Keep your promise.
سأفعل ما أقول لن أسحب
You deserve a beating.
لنذهب لتناول الطعام
Mom, come and eat.
تعال
Why is he always so cheerful?
لماذا أنت سعيد جدا
He's just a kid.
إنه طفل
He'll get sick if he doesn't move.
إنه مريض
He might fall down.
لقد سقط
Yes.
نعم
Xu Yuteng's fan meeting is coming.
اجتماع مقابلة شو يي تينغ على وشك الوصول
I'm looking forward to it.
أتطلع
I'll wait for another minute.
سأنتظر دقيقة أخرى
Maybe next minute
ربما في الدقيقة القادمة
I will see your shy face.
عندما أراك تجنبين
Diqiu?
الأرض
If I remember correctly,
إذا كنت أتذكر بشكل صحيح
it should be "maybe with eyes".
‫ربما يكون العين‬
Two wrong words in one sentence.
غناء كلمة خاطئة
You're so stupid.
أنت غبي
What's the difference?
ما الفرق
Wei Xing.
vệ tinh
Do you have time for the fan meeting?
هل يمكنك تجهيز الوقت لمقابلتك؟
I don't know.
لا أعرف
During that time
في ذلك الوقت
I might be in the art exams.
ربما في امتحان الفنون الجميلة
The fan meeting is the memory of youth.
حفل اللقاء هو ذكريات الشباب
In 50 years,
بعد خمسين سنة
you may not remember the present,
قد لا تتذكر الآن
but you will remember Xu Yuteng.
لكن بالتأكيد ستتذكر شو يي تينغ
-Okay. -Let’s go.
حسنًا لنذهب
You're always full of nonsense.
أنت دائمًا ماكر
Wait for me!
انتظروني
Look! Look!
انظر بسرعة
Am I pretty?
هل أنا جميلة
A concert?
الحفل الغنائي
Yes.
نعم
Are you blind?
هل أنت أعمى؟
The boy from top ten singers is so cool.
هذا الشاب الممثل العشر رائع جدا
Yes, his name is Han Shuai.
نعم اسمه هان سي
They say he comes from a rich family
سمعت أن عائلته غنية جدا
and has good grades.
كما أن أدائه جيد جدا
Just like the male lead in a novel,
مثل البطل الرواية
I wonder what kind of a girl he'll like.
لا أعرف أي نوع من الفتيات يحبها
He doesn't like girls like you anyway.
لا يحب فتاة مثلك على أي حال
You don't look
يبدو أنك
very smart.
ليس ذكيًا جدًا
Does he like you?
هل سيحبك؟
Of course.
بالطبع
I will be the one he likes in the future.
سوف يحبني القائد هان في المستقبل
Handsome.
أيها الوسيم
Read it secretly.
انظر بهدوء
A love letter?
رسالة حب
Just throw it away.
فقط رميها
What are you looking at?
إلام تنظر؟
I've never seen such an unexpected thing.
لم أتلقى مثل هذا الشيء المفاجئ في حياتي
Let me see.
دعني أفتح عيني
Give it back to me.
أعده لي
You bumped into me.
صدمتني
Mr. Han.
المدير هان
The car is downstairs.
السيارة في الأسفل
Okay.
حسنا
You go first.
اذهب أولا
I'll be right there.
سآتي حالاً
What is it?
ما الخطب؟
Do you have something to tell me?
هل هناك شيء تريد أن تقوله لي
Mr. Han,
المدير هان
Look.
انظر
I've been working in the company for years.
لقد عملت في الشركة لسنوات عديدة
I've been working hard.
كنت أعمل بجد
Our company has become a big company.
أصبحت شركتنا شركة كبيرة منذ الصغر
I...
أنا
That means you also think
هذا يعني أنك تعتقد أيضا
the company can't hold on anymore?
الشركة لا تستطيع التحمل
Of course not, Mr. Han.
كيف يمكن ذلك المدير هان
I believe you will
أعتقد أنك
lead the company through difficulties.
ستقود الشركة لتجاوز الصعوبات
But if there is anything new,
لكن إذا كان هناك أي أخبار جديدة من الشركة
I hope you can tell me sooner
آمل أن تخبريني في وقت مبكر
so we can make plans.
يجب أن تخطط مبكرا
Wait for me outside.
انتظرني في الخارج
Okay, Mr. Han.
حسنا المدير هان
By the way, Mr. Han,
صحيح المدير هان
this is from the bank.
هذا من البنك
I'll wait for you downstairs.
سأنتظرك في الطابق السفلي
Wei XIng?
‫وي شينغ
So?
ماذا تقول
Are you going to my house tonight?
هل ستذهب إلى منزلي الليلة؟
Not tonight.
لا أظن ذلك اليوم
I have to draw the blackboard tonight.
يجب أن أصنع الصحيفة في المساء
Is it so?
لصنع الصحيفة
Go to his house.
إلى منزله
Wei Xing is going to his house.
‫سيذهب وي شينغ إلى منزله
Let's talk outside.
لنتحدث في الخارج
What's wrong? It's not during classtime.
‏ما الخطب؟ أليست هذه صف؟‏
Excuse me.
أيها الزميل
Please be quiet in the classroom.
يرجى الهدوء في الفصل
Vice President Li.
نائب الرئيس لي
You have a tamper again, right?
هل تناولت المسدس مرة أخرى؟
Wei XIng?
‫وي شينغ
You're a senior now.
الآن في الثانوية
You should focus on your study.
يجب أن تركز على الدراسة
Don't let someone affect you.
.لا تؤثر عليك بسبب شخص ما
Li Jin.
"."لي جين
Are you looking for trouble again?
هل تبحث عن المشاكل مرة أخرى؟
Let's go.
هيا
Just take care of yourself.
اهتم بنفسك
Wei Xing, wait for me.
وي شينغ انتظرني
Mr. Han,
سيد هان
we comprehended all aspects
لقد جمعنا جميع شروط الزميل هان
and interests for Han.
والتخصص
And we think these American schools
أعتقد أن الأكاديمية في الولايات المتحدة
can be considered.
يمكن التفكير
Especially UCSD
خاصة UCSD جامعة غاليفونيا
and NYU.
‫وهذان الأكاديمية في جامعة نيو
Their finances are ranked top in the US.
قسم التمويل في الأوائل في الجمال
Actually,
في الواقع
I've learned about it before.
لقد عرفت من قبل
It seems that
يبدو
some colleges in Japan are good.
بعض الأكاديمية في اليابان جيدة أيضا
With your financial strength,
مع قدرتك الاقتصادية يا سيد هان
you don't have to choose the Japanese ones
لا تحتاج إلى اختيار مدرسة يابانية
unless you want him to be closer to home.
وإلا لا تحتاج إلى اختيار مدرسة يابانية
What do you think, Han?
لا أعرف ما رأيك
He must go to the American schools.
بالتأكيد سنذهب إلى مدرسة أمريكية
What's good about schools in Japan?
ما الممتع بالمدرسة اليابانية
Right, dad?
أليس كذلك يا أبي
And our family doesn't lack that much money.
ولا ينقصنا المال
That's also our suggestion.
اقتراحنا هكذا أيضا
Drink slowly.
اشرب ببطء اشرب ببطء
Give me a few hundred thousand more.
أعطني مئات ألف أخرى
I'll definitely manage the company.
يمكنني بالتأكيد أن أحل الشركة
I was so close.
ينقصني القليل فقط
But now,
الآن
Shuai is going to study abroad.
وسيم سيذهب للدراسة في الخارج
And I can’t even support him.
لا أملك الشجاعة لدعمه.
You must have many friends
لقد عملت لسنوات عديدة
after all these years in business.
يجب أن يكون لديك الكثير من الأصدقاء
You are too prideful.
أنت حقا تحترم ماء وجهك
Don't be like me.
لا تكوني مثلي
When something happens, you have to say it.
عليك أن تفتح فمك عندما تكون في مشكلة
Lower your head when you should.
يجب أن تستسلم
We are friends when we are rich.
نحن أصدقاء عندما نكون غنيين
If we don't have money...
إذا نفدت المال
I envy you two.
أنتما الاثنين أفضل
One is doing a small business,
واحد يقوم بأعمال صغيرة
while the other is a factory technician.
أحدهما يدير التكنولوجيا في المصنع
No matter what happens outside,
إذا حدث شيء بالخارج
it will not affect you.
لن يؤثر عليكم
It does.
وتأثر أيضا
Now,
الآن
these things are not easy to sell.
هذا الشيء ليس من السهل بيعه
The purchase price has increased a lot.
لقد ارتفع سعر التسليم كثيرا
Wang, you are not affected.
‫لاو وانغ لن تتأثر
Have you heard of an old saying?
هل سمعت هذا من قبل؟
A craftsman can't starve in a crisis.
‫لا يمكن أن يموت فنان الحرفيين بالجوع
I work in the factory.
أنا أعمل في المصنع
I'm not as successful as you,
على الرغم من أنني لست أفضل منك
but I'm doing technical work.
لكن ما أفعله هو العمل التكنولوجي
The technical industry
المهنة التكنولوجية
won't be easily affected.
لن يتأثر بسهولة
I admire you.
أنا معجب بك
Come on.
هيا
To technology.
نخب التكنولوجيا
Yes.
نعم
Director.
أيها المدير
This...
هذا
Are you mistaken?
هل أخطأت؟
Jianmin,
جيان مين
don't be too resistant.
لا تتردد كثيراً
Now,
الآن
you know the big environment.
أنت تعرف هذه البيئة الكبيرة
Our factory
إن المصنع
has difficulties.
في المصنع
No.
لا
This...
هذا
Director,
أيها المدير
you have to help me.
عليك مساعدتي في إيجاد طريقة
My family is waiting for me to support them.
عائلتي بأكملها تنتظرني
Look.
انظر
I've never been late.
لم أتأخر قط
I'm an advanced worker every year.
كل عام أعمل متقدم
Well,
هذه الطريقة
there is a solution.
ليس لا يوجد
It depends on
‫انظر‬
whether your brain
عقلك
is brilliant.
هل أنت ذكي؟
What is it?
ما هي الطريقة
Money.
المال
Director, you have a sore throat.
أيها المدير إن حلقك غير مرتاح
Let me get you some water.
سأحضر لك بعض الماء
Sit down.
اجلس
Come here.
تعال تعال تعال
Jianmin.
جيان مين
Do you know why you can't be promoted
هل تعرف لماذا
for so many years?
في هذه السنوات
Your brain
هذا هو عقلك
is too short-sighted.
غير ذكي للغاية
I can help you.
يمكنني مساعدتك
But...
لكن
Don't you think
هل تعتقد
that we need to pull some strings?
هل يجب أن نتحرك؟
Shouldn't we need money
إذاً لنتحرك
for that?
ألا يجب أن يكون هناك بعض المال
You want money?
هل تريد المال؟
What are you saying?
ماذا تقول؟
I don't need your money.
هل يمكنني أن ينقصك قليلا
I'm helping you.
أنا أساعدك في النشاط
How much is it?
كم ثمن ذلك؟
Do as you wish.
افعل ما يحلو لك
I heard that
سمعت
Wei Xing in our class
‫وي شينغ في صفنا
is with Diqiu in yours.
‏مع الأرض‏
Really?
حقا
I heard they already live together.
‏سمعت أنّنا نعيش معاً‏
Wang Diqiu said it himself.
‏قال ملك الأرض ذلك‏
Say it.
‏أخبريني‏
Wei Xing.
‫وي شينغ
Let's go play basketball.
لنذهب للعب
Why are you alone?
لماذا أنت وحدك؟
Han Shuai.
القائد هان
He went to that agency
ذهب إلى
in PE class.
إلى نادي الدراسة بالخارج
Ting.
تينغ تينغ
I don't know what she's doing.
لا أعرف ماذا تفعل
Go play basketball.
لنلعب الكرة الطائرة
Go find someone else.
اذهبي للبحث عن شخص آخر
Today,
اليوم
I don't want to play basketball.
لا أريد لعب الكرة الطائرة
Stop.
توقف
Why are you back so early today?
لماذا عدت مبكرا اليوم
Well,
حسناً
there's a power outage today.
انقطع الكهرباء اليوم
All of our factories are closed.
‫جميع المصنع في هذا المكان يستريح
Let me help you.
سأساعدك
Is the sun rising from the west?
إنها الشمس تخرج من الغرب
I work every day.
أنا أعمل كل يوم
I can't take care of home.
ولا أهتم بالمنزل
Today is my day off.
ليس من السهل الحصول على يوم عطلة اليوم
I have to do some chores for my wife,
يجب أن أتحمل بعض الأعمال المنزلية لزوجتي
right?
أليس كذلك
Are you hiding something from me?
هل تخفي شيئًا عني؟
No.
لا
I heard that
سمعت
the big environment is not good recently.
أن البيئة الكبيرة ليست جيدة مؤخرًا
Don't worry.
اطمئن
I do technical work in the factory.
أنا أعمل في المصنع
I'm a hit.
شهية جدا
I need to cook.
يجب أن أطبخ
You fold it.
‏اقطفها‏
Handsome, we are all from Class 8.
‏نحن من الصف الثامن‏
Can we be QQ friends?
‏هل يمكنني إضافة (كيو كيو)؟‏
Come on.
أضف واحدة
We came all the way here for you.
لقد جئنا إلى هنا خصيصاً للبحث عنك
That's right.
نعم نعم
Come on.
إضافة واحدة
We are in the same class.
نحن في نفس الصف
Add me.
لنضيف
Forget it.
انسي الأمر
Just add me.
أضف المزيد
I also want to ask you about knowledge.
أريد أن أسألك عن الدراسة
Add me.
أضيفها
Why not?
ما المشكلة
Add one.
أضف واحدة
Add it.
‫أضيفها‬
Get out of my way.
افسحوا الطريق
Add me.
أضف المزيد
No, no.
لا أضيف لا أضيف
Come on.
أضف
No.
لا
I'm sorry.
آسف آسف
I didn't mean it.
لم أقصد ذلك
Guo Ting.
قوه تينغ
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف
This is not the first time.
هذا ليس مرة أو مرتين
I'm used to it.
لقد اعتدت على ذلك
Here.
تفضل
Help me shake it.
‫ساعديني بالتدليك‬
Hurry up.
بسرعة
Okay.
حسنا
This is the brochure...
هذا
For studying in America.
كتاب الدراسة في الولايات المتحدة
I forgot to take it out in a hurry.
لقد نسيت أن آخذه
Are you really going to America?
هل ستذهبين إلى أمريكا حقا
Didn't you know?
ألم تعرف ذلك منذ وقت طويل؟
But America is too far away.
لكن الولايات المتحدة بعيدة جدا
You should have told me and Wang
وأنت تقدمت بطلب رسمي
if you have officially applied.
وأخبر لاو وانغ
I haven't officially applied yet.
‫ألم تقدم بطلب رسمي بعد‬
I've made up my mind.
لقد قررت
I will go to the US's best finance college.
سأذهب إلى أكبر جامعة مالية في أمريكا
I, Han Shuai,
أنا وسيم هان
when I study abroad,
أو لا أدرس في الخارج
I must go to the best place.
إذا أردت الدراسة في الخارج يجب أن تذهب إلى أفضل مكان
Turn around.
استديري
You do it yourself.
أنت تهتز بنفسك
Hey.
ألو
What happened?
ماذا حدث
Did Diqiu make you unhappy again?
الأرض تجعلك غير سعيد مرة أخرى
If...
إذا
I mean if.
أعني لو
If the protagonist of your novel
بطلك الرواية
fell in love with someone impossible,
وقعت في حب شخص لا يمكن أن نكون معا
what should she do?
ماذا ستفعل؟
Why impossible?
لماذا لا يمكن
There are many reasons.
هناك العديد من الأسباب
That's what it's like in dramas.
أليس هذا ما تمثله في المسلسلات
Parents don't agree.
والداي لا يوافقون
There is another person.
الشخص الثالث يدخل
Also,
بالإضافة إلى ذلك
he has to go far away.
سيذهب إلى مكان بعيد جدا
Actually, love
في الواقع الحب
is not impossible.
لا يوجد الكثير من المستحيل
The so-called impossible
ما يسمى مستحيل
is just
♫ إنه الحب ببعضنا ♫
making choices
في الحب
between love
والأشياء الأكثر أهمية
and more important things.
بين الأشياء المهمة
Of course,
بالطبع
if the ending is that they are
إذا كانت النهاية
not meant to be together,
لا يمكن أن نكون معا
I'd rather
فأنا على استعداد
they never met each other.
لم يلتقيا في البداية
Love is so troublesome.
الحب مزعج جدا
Well,
إذا
Look.
انظر
If only we could be care-free
إذا استطعنا أن نكون مثل هذه الطيور
like these birds.
مثل هذه الطيور
Ting,
تينغ تينغ
besides love,
في الواقع باستثناء الحب
there are many interesting things in life.
هناك الكثير من الأشياء الممتعة في الحياة
For example?
على سبيل المثال
Look.
انظر
The reason birds are happy is because
إن الطائر الصغير سعيد جدا
there's only one thing in their mind.
لأن هناك شيء واحد في ذهنهم
That is to find today's food.
هو العثور على الطعام اليوم
We are the same.
إننا إنسان نفس الشيء
When you find
عندما تجد
a goal
أنك على استعداد
to work hard for,
من أجل الهدف
happiness becomes simple.
‫أصبحت السعادة بسيطة‬
A goal?
أهداف؟
The target.
‏هدف؟‏
You're not doing your homework hard
ليس نشيطا في كتابة الواجبات
or copying hard.
لا نشيط في نسخ الواجبات
Comrade Guo Ting,
الزميل قوه تينغ
what are you going to do?
يا رفيق ماذا ستفعل
Are you frozen?
لقد مات
Leave me alone.
لا تزعجني
I'm thinking about life.
أنا أفكر في شيء مهم في الحياة
Life?
شيء مهم في الحياة
Take it easy.
اعتني بنفسك
Be careful not to overheat your brain.
احذر من الحمى
I don't want to talk to you.
لا أريد التحدث معك
Brother.
أخي
Oh no.
سأذهب
Are you copying the answers?
هل نسخ الجواب؟
I have something to do. I have to go.
أنا مشغول سأذهب
Where are you going?
إلى أين
Ting.
تينغ تينغ
Is Ting unhappy?
هل تينغ تينغ حزينة
Who knows?
من يعرف
She didn't talk to methis afternoon.
سألتها بعد الظهر ولم تخبرني
She must be trapped in some tragic novel
لا بد أنها وقعت في الرواية الحزينة
and can't get out.
لا يمكن التخلص منها
Leave her alone.
تجاهلها
Wei Xing.
‫وي شينغ
I have to go back.
لدي شيء يجب أن أعود
You too.
عودي باكراً
Goodbye, Ms. Chen. Bye.
إلى اللقاء يا أستاذ تشين
Bye.
مع السلامة
By the way,
بالمناسبة
is Wei Xing in school doing the blackboard?
هل سيبقى وي شينغ في المدرسة لصنع الصحيفة السوداء؟
This is a heavy task.
هذه المهمة ثقيلة
I think it will take a long time.
أعتقد أن الوقت متأخر جدا
Look at her. Look at her.
أي فتاة
Going home alone?
ستعود إلى المنزل وحدها
Wang Diqiu.
‫وانغ الأرض‬
Wei Xing.
‫vệ tinh‬
I'm here to pick you up.
جئت لأخذك